This may be the biggest mission of this strenuous project.
Wait a minute! Wait a minute! Wait a minute! Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
Whoa!
What is this food?
This is really delicious!
Hello, I'm Kyo Onuma from Sakurazaka 46.
This time, I'm going to try my favorite fishing project on YouTube.
Yay!
Ta-da! I would like to go to the fishing tackle shop here now.
Okay, I'm going.
It's my first time going to a fishing tackle shop, and I'm really looking forward to it.
It's amazing.
Wow! It's a really big fishing tackle shop.
Fishing, wow!
There's so much stuff, wow!
Wow, really!
I was fooled by this.
The fishes are caught by the humans.
I've been fishing since I was really little.
I used to fish with my father.
We used to catch a lot of fish.
I used to catch 18 scorpionfish in a day.
But I've never caught that many big fish.
So my goal this time was to catch
I want to buy a lure and a fishing rod
I thought it would be nice to buy a fishing rod and lure to catch such a big fish, like a big sea bream.
I found a fishing rod.
Here it is, a fishing rod!
10% off. All of them.
All of them? Isn't that great?
Oh, I found it.
Wow. Koga.
I've been wanting one of these.
I think this is probably the most popular one.
But I already have some kouga.But I have a few more koogas.
I guess I should ask the shopkeeper.
I'm usually not good at talking to store clerks.
I'm a little scared because I've never been able to talk to them myself.
This may be the biggest mission of the fishing project.
Talking to them...
I don't know if I should just say, "Hi, excuse me.
Hello, hello.
How do I talk to him?
Excuse me, I have a fishing rod I'm interested in.
Can I talk to you about it?
Sure, go ahead.
Thank you very much.
You're very kind.
It's so nice to meet you.
I'm interested in Konohe.
I'm wondering if there are different grades in the same series of Hung River.
I see.
In this area, it's usually about one sheet.
I'm interested in this rod, but I'm not sure if it can be used for other than Thai.
Does that mean you can catch other fish with this rod?
You want to fish for horse mackerel with a light weight in Tokyo Bay?
It can also be used for that kind of thing.
So it can be used for that?
It looks light.
It's so light!
And the cheeks are pink and cute!
I'd like to buy this one.
Yay!
Oh!
This is it!
There it is!
It's a big rubber, and it's a lure to catch fish, and it's very specialized for fishing. Isn't it cute?
It's like a Chiba lure, but for fish.It looks like it's a good one. It looks like Chiba, and it looks like it's going to be popular with the fish.
I wonder if it's okay to use this tie-ruba.
I bought a fishing rod from Kobe, but is this lure okay?
I bought a fishing rod from Kobe... and I was wondering if it would be okay with this lure.
It's when I live here...
It's a different lure for typhoon days.
I've learned a lot. Give me this.
Here you go.
I'm going to buy a fishing rod for rock trout.
This one's cute, too.
It's cute.
It looks like Doraemon.
This one is really cool too.
Sabikizuri?
Japanese Spanish mackerel (Scomber japonicus)
It says that black sea bream, sea bream, and sea bream are OK too!
It would be great if I could catch black sea bream with this!
I have to buy a cooler box too!
There was a cooler box!
Wow, there are so many kinds of cooler boxes!
What should I do?
If you definitely want to catch big fish
I think you should definitely get a big one.
but it's really heavy!
Wait a minute!
Wow!
It's surprisingly small.
It's small but heavy.
How much does it weigh?
It looks like it weighs about 50 kg.
But will it hold fish?
This is really good, isn't it?
Oh, wow.
But, I'll take this...
I'll put this on the train, for example.Hold this, for example, on the train.
Hold it.
It's white.
And it doesn't look like a fashionable bag.
I'll take this one then.
This one.
I'll take this one.
I used to have this at home. It's like a slogan... "You'll attract, you'll make them eat, you'll catch fish.
Like a fish slogan. Now I can go fishing.
Yes!
It's the most expensive purchase I've made this year, but now that I've bought everything I want, I feel so much better.
It's so refreshing.
That's right, I wanted to say "refreshing"!
So, here we are at the fishing spot!
Yes, yes!
With this fishing rod on my back!
I haven't been fishing for a while.
I haven't fished in like five years.
Do you think I'll be able to catch it?
I'm excited!
I'm going to do my best.
I'm going to put bait on it.
Ta-da!
It looks like this.
I'd like to put this on the hook.
Ta-da!
This is the bait.
I like this very much.
It feels good.
Here we go.
This looks like it.
Mountain cold, lake...
I'm in the middle of my first sabiki fishing...I'm in the middle of my first sabiki fishing.
I wonder how it's going, and if I'll be able to catch any fish.
I don't feel like the fish are eating at all.
I want to catch at least one fish for sure.
I want to show the fish I caught to everyone who is watching this site.
I'll do my best.
I wonder if I can catch it.
Oh!
What? I don't know.
Whoa!
Whoa! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey!
What?
It's gone!
Are you sure it's not stuck?
It happens, doesn't it?
I thought I was getting pulled in a little bit.
I thought it was just tangled up or something, so I pulled it out.
I felt a great fish, so I tried pulling it back.
It was a little bit too shallow.
Well, the fish wasn't stuck yet, but...
I'm off!
Can you go?
Let's go!
Here we go.
But I missed one earlier.
The girl you missed.
Can you come back?
I think he's learned his lesson.
My favorite fish, if it's a fish face, is the boxfish.
I think it's so cute because of its boxy shape and its big eyes.
If I had to eat tuna, I would say tuna is my favorite.
But how do you catch tuna?
I often see people fishing for tuna on TV.
I don't think I could ever catch tuna myself.I don't think I could ever catch it myself.
Oh?
I think he's here.
No, no.
Oh!
Oh, here it comes!
What happens now that they're here? He might get away again.
What? They're here, aren't they?
Whoa! They're here!
Oh, please! Please! Please! Please! Please!
Please!
Please! Please! Please!
Hey, please! Please! Please! Please! Please!
Please! Please! Please! Please! Please! Please!
Please! Please! Please! Please!
Whoa! Wait!
Why? !
I'm so shocked.
What? Why?
Was that a little fast?
What? But slowly.
I was going too slow!
Why?
Here we go.
But there's something about the sound of the ocean... and the wind... and the weather...
And the wind, and the weather, and the time when we don't fish...
I think the best thing about fishing is that it's so relaxing.
I don't know.
I like the feeling of being able to relax and forget about everyday life.
Oh, he might be here.
Oh, no, they're not.
It's pulling like crazy.
Wow, it's amazing!Oh, my gosh.
I'm going to be a little careful.
Oh, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
Oh, wow. Oh, wow.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, wow. Oh, wow.
Oh, my gosh, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Oh, my God, I caught it.
Yay!
Oh, I'm so happy.
That's amazing!
There it is, right here in the water.
Oh, yeah!
I caught it!
We did it!
This fish is called a konoshiro.
It's the birthplace of kohada.
The birth fish.
It's the birthfish of kohada.
Really?
Thank you so much for coming.
We're all very happy to see you.
We're so happy.
So...
Well, I caught one today.
Yay! - Yay!
No, unfortunately, two got away.
Actually, I had three fish.
But this is the depth of fishing.
I think it was fun to be entertained by such a great fish!
Next time, I've bought another good fishing rod
I'd like to try again with that one.
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating!Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating!
Yes, I'd like to start to serve the fish now!
By the way, I named him Shiro.
This Shiro, Shiro-chan.
Shiro-chan.
I'm going to cut it into pieces.
I think.
In three pieces.
I made them take it off.
Put Mr. White in.
Ta-da!
Put it in.
Seasoning.
Soy sauce.
Sugar.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
I'll put it in the potato starch!
bye bye bye
I'd like to try deep frying alone
Let's go!
What?
Are you okay?
Oh, is he okay?
Wow, wow, wow!
Oh, my gosh!
Here we go.
That's good.
Again.
Yes!
Wow!
It's so big!
Wow, wait a minute.Wow, wait a minute.
what's going on?
Hello, everything's fine.
Fried food?
Wow, he's back again.
How did you do that?
Don't do that.
All right.
Woah.
Whoo-hoo!
The fried fish casserole is ready.
Ta-da!
Isn't it great? Bon appétit!
Yum!
It's so delicious!
I think it was a good decision to deep fry it.
What is this food?
It's really delicious.
Yes, it is.
It's so good! I have a bone in my throat now.
Well, I'm sorry about the small things.
I finished it.
Thank you for the food.
Bye-bye. Finished.
A teacher said to me.
That you shave your eyebrows.
I don't. I've never shaved them.
They're just thin to begin with.
I argued with the teacher.
She'll just think I'm a bad kid.
And I'm like, "Okay, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I gave up. My eyebrows.
If I'm going to go home and cry...
I wonder if you would've believed me if I'd cried out in front of the Giant God back then.
I wonder if you would've believed me if I'd cried out in front of the Giant GodIf I had cried out, would you have believed me?
You can't express your feelings unless you show them.
I'm not good at getting angry or crying in public.
I don't know how to express my feelings.
I'm sorry I'm like this. My eyebrows.
My eyebrows.
Is the world a place where the law of the jungle is the law of the jungle?
My eyebrow.
I was weak, so I couldn't help you?
I only have two eyebrows.
My eyebrows.
I have to fight to protect me so that I can be me.
Because I can't live
I can't live